engineeringbookspdf.com 2013-10-16

# Privacy Policy - EngineeringBooksPDF

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

 **Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

[EngineeringBooksPDF.com](http://engineeringbookspdf.com/) has no access or [control](http://engineeringbookspdf.com/tag/control/ "control") over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

 **Our Commitment To Childrens Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, EngineeringBooksPDF.com will never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.  
Under our Terms of Service, children under 18 are not allowed to access our service.

 **Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting [EngineeringBooksPDF.com](http://engineeringbookspdf.com/), the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

 **Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

 **Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of EngineeringBooksPDF.com then you may [contact us](http://engineeringbookspdf.com/contact-us/).
